Jinwoo. you've changed a lot.
Yet. I remain the same.
So much has happened to me.
Everyone benefits differently
from their experiences.
That's true.
As a hunter.
I seem to be too timid.
Although I've tried to overcome it.
it's too hard.
Logically. I should be
taking part in A-rank or B-rank
or at least C-rank missions.
Yet. I always choose D-rank
or E-rank ones.
That's why I got to know you.
Looking back. it seems like
I was always treating you.
Honestly. when you kept
getting injured at the beginning.
I found you a bit annoying.
But Jinwoo.
you always survive.
Your eyes are brimming with life.
and I'll never forget them.
We agreed to have a meal together. right?
Here.
Take it back.
Are you...
Actually.
I've decided to retire.
I plan to go back to my hometown.
If you happen to come nearby.
please let me know.
I'll take you out to enjoy the view.
By then.
we'll have a meal together.
Okay.
I don't think you at E-rank can
defeat Kang Taeshik at B-rank.
I don't want to suspect again
that you had second awakening.
But I still want to tell you.
if you want to live longer.
be more careful.
What do you mean?
In the annihilation incident
of Hwang Dongsuk's team.
the only survivors were
you and a D-rank hunter.
Hwang Dongsuk's brother.
hunter Hwang Dongsoo.
may already set his sights on you.
S-rank hunter Hwang Dongsoo
has set his sights on me?
Yes.
What happened
in the dungeon isn't important.
The fact is Hwang Dongsuk died
and you came back alive.
He is an S-rank hunter.
The law cannot restrain him.
His existence is both
a miracle and a disaster.
The monster that even monsters fear
will very likely to come after you.
That's it.
If possible.
I think you'd better leave
this country with your family.
I have another reason to become stronger.
I must become stronger.
Only then can I survive.
Um...
Jinho.
Why are these people here?
Them?
Isn't that obvious?
They are members of our team.
Those hunters
who are unable to work for some reason
and those living in poverty
are my priority targets.
The disabled and drunkards.
That's more convenient for us.
We need at least eight members
to enter a C-rank dungeon.
Hey. why is there a kid?
Awakened minors can also participate.
It's not illegal.
Hey.
You're being quite rude.
I am a real hunter.
But you're a high-schooler. right?
Were you ever in a raid mission?
Er... I haven't.
Are you an E-rank hunter?
So what?
Never mind.
You're just waiting outside anyway.
Only Jinho and I will enter the dungeon.
Um...
Is it really just you two going in?
We get three million
just by waiting outside?
Yes.
Three million for one raid mission.
You get money without
having to fight. isn't it nice?
But this must be kept secret.
If I find out you didn't.
you'll be charged ten times
the reward as per the contract.
The stealth rune stone I got
after defeating Kang Taeshik.
I'll try it now.
Good.
Looks like I've learned it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's with this kit?
This is an enhanced armor set made
by the Italian Artisans' Guild.
After all. only the two of us
are going into the dungeon.
I have to make some preparation.
Take my advice and get it off.
Yes.
Jinwoo.
Can you pull me up?
Then let's set off.
I'm starting to feel a bit nervous.
You haven't taken
that thing off your head.
At least let me wear a helmet.
Alright.
Let's go.
Yes.
They're really going in by themselves.
Will they be okay?
We've already warned them.
We've already got the money.
so just leave them alone.
A D-rank hunter and an E-rank hunter
want to tackle a C-rank raid mission?
Two greenhorns.
It's not as easy as they thought.
Did Song-yi skip class?
How long has it been?
About an hour.
Even a regular team would
take about two hours.
It won't be that...
You managed to escape?
Lucky for you.
No.
They didn't escape.
The gate is closing.
No way.
Did they defeat the Boss?
Where's the next gate?
It takes an hour to get there.
Understood. let's go.
Everyone. we are leaving.
We have three places to go today.
You can earn nine million in just one day.
Don't you want to go?
These two...
Who are they?
Jinwoo. I'm all done.
Understood.
I'll take care of it.
I'm heading out.
You're going to work today too?
Yeah. can you lock the door?
He even has such a skill.
He seems to have gotten even stronger.
Skill. Stealth.
Although the process of obtaining
this skill was unpleasant.
this skill is very useful.
Using stealth in fights is very efficient.
The skill level of Dash has increased?
New skills.
Advanced Dagger Wielding and Fatal Strike.
Great skills too.
You've worked hard. Jinwoo.
I'm almost done collecting.
You take a rest first.
Hmm. go ahead.
I have more interesting skills now.
But no matter which skill.
it's limited by its duration.
which means I don't have enough MP.
It seems I also need
to increase my intelligence.
All right.
It's going well. but should I head
straight to the Demon's Castle?
No.
My current strength should be
above B-rank and below A-rank.
Am I capable of challenging that dungeon?
The player has reached the required level.
A Job-change quest?
Please take a look at this.
Chief Ahn.
Hmm?
What's up. Kichul?
This is the bidding document
for the C-rank gate.
150 million?
Someone spent 150 million
to conquer a C-rank gate?
Yes.
There's a raid team
that bid double the market price
for every C-rank gate lately.
Their Captain is
Yoo Jinho?
I've never heard of this person.
He is the second son
of the Yoojin Construction's chairman.
Yoojin Construction?
He might cause his company to lose money.
Even if it's a rich kid having fun.
he's gone too far.
Sung Jinwoo. an E-rank hunter?
Yes.
Their members are also
put together temporarily.
I have no idea what they're trying to do.
No.
The name Sung Jinwoo
also appeared in
the double dungeon incident.
There's something fishy.
There definitely is.
Hey. wait.
I won.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
No. it's okay.
You came back earlier than expected.
Collecting mana crystals
took longer than I thought.
All right. let's go.
You must be tired too.
Do you want me to drive?
Eh?
I am getting restless from boredom.
At least let me do something.
I see.
What?
-Nothing.
-We agreed for you to wait outside.
You don't need to do anything more.
What? Hunter Sung Jinwoo
is a second awakener?
Yes. that's right.
Do you have any proof?
Hunter Sung has had three major incidents.
yet he came out unscathed every time.
The first was the double dungeon incident.
The second was annihilation incident
of the Hwang Dongsuk's team.
The third was
the incident of prisoners being killed
by the surveillance department hunter.
Nearly all participants
in these events died.
Yet he survived.
If he's not a second awakener.
there's no way to explain this.
That... is true.
By the way. Chief Ahn.
where are we going?
Where else?
To scout for new talent.
What's this?
It's like they're having a picnic.
Mister.
this area is currently off-limits.
Ah. sorry about that.
I was just curious because it looked
like hunters were gathering here.
That's a gate. right?
Are you sure it's okay to stand so close?
Please don't treat me like a child.
I am a hunter too.
Eh? Are you...
Are you also with this team?
Yes.
Eh?
But...
Hunter Sung
went in without the rest of the team.
If I'm not mistaken.
he must be a rare strong one.
No. a super strong one.
I see.
I apologize for disturbing you.
Please be careful.
Eh? Are we leaving. Chief?
The Captain is out.
Everyone. prepare to leave.
Do you have any tasks
scheduled for tomorrow?
I'm busy tomorrow.
Should we take a day off?
Ah... tomorrow?
I do have a gate reserved.
Should I cancel it?
Don't cancel if you've reserved it.
That'd be a waste of money.
I can keep it for two days.
Then keep it for now.
I understand.
Thank you for waiting.
Alright. let's head to the next one.
That dream again?
The day is approaching.
Well. thank you. everyone.
Excuse me for intruding. Hunter Sung.
Nice to meet you.
I am Ahn Sangmin from the White Tiger
Guild's second management division.
May we have a chat with you?
I believe I don't need to
elaborate further.
Our White Tiger Guild is
one of the best in the country.
So we are always looking
for outstanding talents.
Let me get straight to the point.
We can offer you twice as much money
as Yoojin Construction can offer
if you join our White Tiger Guild.
If you have any conditions.
I will do my best to satisfy them.
How is it?
For someone who was
an E-rank hunter not long ago.
this offer must be a chance
you cannot refuse.
I will make you say yes.
How much is the market value
of White Tiger Guild's building?
What?
Well... it's probably worth
around fifty billion.
So. do you plan to give
me the entire building?
I don't quite understand.
Thirty billion?
Did you hear that?
The terms offered to me
by Yoojin Construction
is a building with a market
value of thirty billion.
You said you would pay me double.
I thought you were going to give me
that fifty-billion building.
If you don't believe me.
I can prove it here.
But...
Such a large amount
is beyond my authority.
I need to discuss it with my superiors.
Then this is the end of the topic.
Huh? Ah.
Was I too hasty?
I should have investigated the terms
offered by Yoojin Construction first.
Right. by the way.
how did you know about me?
Have you been
secretly investigating me?
Huh?
Where is he?
This... this is
a Stealth skill.
So he is a second awakener
with a Stealth skill.
No wonder Yoojin Construction
offered him such a large sum.
I... I apologize for investigating
you without permission.
But I meant no malice.
Don't look back.
Because someone is
monopolizing the dungeons.
it prevents us from
training our newcomers.
According to company regulations.
they can't be deployed
in actual combat without training.
To negotiate the deal regarding gates.
we found you when we
investigated the person
who was buying up dungeons.
Besides you. how many
others know about me?
Just me and one of my subordinates.
I don't want anyone to know about me.
If rumors about me spread.
you will be the first person I suspect.
I have an obligation
to report to the guild.
But I don't want to die.
I will also keep my subordinate silent.
Thank you.
It seems our monopoly of C-rank gates
has caused you some trouble.
I apologize.
But this situation will
continue for a while.
That's going to be difficult.
In that case. we will be
unable to train newcomers.
Then would you like
to make a deal with me?
A deal?
I can sell you three C-rank
gates we have reserved.
If you don't take it.
you can't get access to
a C-rank dungeon for a while.
He is using hunger marketing
to lure me in.
But...
I understand.
How much are they?
Three hundred million for each.
Three... Three hundred million?
The mana crystals and
magic gems in a C-rank dungeon
are worth at most two hundred million.
I hope the price can be lowered
to two hundred million...
Okay.
Eh?
Deal.
Then...
You will give us three gates. right?
Yes. three C-rank gates.
Six hundred million in total.
Then it's settled.
Please transfer the money
into this account today.
And another thing.
I have a gift for you.
Can you close your eyes
and open your mouth?
Eh?
Don't worry. I won't hurt you.
Really?
My wound has healed.
Goodbye.
Since you have shown me these abilities.
can I take it that
I have earned your trust?
On the condition that you keep my secret.
Chief.
How did it go?
Hey. Kichul.
He might be stronger than we imagined.
Jinwoo. I've received the money.
Six hundred million has
been transferred to me.
How did you sell the gates we
planned to cancel for such a high price?
Who did you sell them to?
That's a trade secret.
What?
There are still C-rank
gates left in our area?
Yes. Yoojin Construction only
bid on those three gates.
Current bidding price are all
below seventy million.
We've been tricked.
Not only did I fail to poach him.
I even got tricked.
What a disgrace.
Is this how the strong are?
A message.
Who sent it?
This is Sung Jinwoo.
With this. we're even. I'll forget
the fact that you spied on me.
I see.
He tricked me.
I admit defeat this time.
He is not to be underestimated.
Was is from Hunter Sung?
Yes.
Although he tricked me this time.
I managed to get his phone number.
I'll compromise this time.
A job-change quest.
How exciting.